Starstruck is a romance, comedy, tv movie film directed by Michael Grossman.
Pop star Christopher Wilde has fame, fortune and a
big-budget Hollywood movie awaiting him.
But after meeting Jessica Olson, a down-to-earth girl from the Midwest, he is
faced with following his heart or doing what's best for his career.
Christopher Wilde, played by Sterling Knight.
Jessica Olson, played by Danielle Campbell.
Albert Joshua "Stubby" Stubbins, played by Brandon Mychal Smith.
Alexis, played by Chelsea Kane.
Sara Olson, played by Maggie Castle.
Alan Smith, played by Matt Winston.
Starstruck, stylized as StarStruck, is a 2010 American teen musical drama television film starring Sterling
Knight and Danielle Campbell that premiered as a Disney Channel Original Movie on February 14, 2010.
The film explores themes of beach, sibling
relationship, pop singer, paparazzi, romcom.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.